<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mfbloge</title>
    <link>https://www.maxfettes.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mfbloge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Max Fettes 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 19:28:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.maxfettes.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliens</title>
      <link>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/aliens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:23:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/aliens/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Be humble, Earthlings.&amp;rsquo; I know about filters already, thank you. I did not need to read this again that yes we are either doomed and leaving behind an astro-archaeolgist&amp;rsquo;s wet dream, or we are not doomed and a statistical anomaly. I did not need this heavy emotional response to the mistakes of the last century (to say the least), and the wrench of gut from Mr. Obvious that our multiverse cousins who sat down and spent some $18^12 on interstellar exploration instead of a world war are in a better place right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FORM</title>
      <link>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/form/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 11:12:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/form/</guid>
      <description>#a colourful sort
&amp;lsquo;Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s because it is very enjoyable.&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;But perhaps you&amp;rsquo;d say that it isn&amp;rsquo;t compatible with our community&amp;rsquo;s political system,&amp;rsquo; I went on, &amp;lsquo;because each of our people has a single job to do, and therefore none of them is two-sided or many-sided.&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;That&amp;rsquo;s right: it&amp;rsquo;s incompatible.&amp;rsquo; - Republic: &amp;lsquo;Primary Education for the Guardians.&amp;rsquo;
They are talking about whether or not to remove certain lines and passages from the Poets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sahi</title>
      <link>https://www.maxfettes.com/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 19:28:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.maxfettes.com/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Fragment Peaceful crossing the road is easy with the shops unlit on order from the popehead. Don&amp;rsquo;t want Pauly not a lick and not polluted not through gas if the grid&amp;rsquo;s not coal. Ivory tower dome, do the blessed nuns and monks all live it up together? Sacre-coeur! Activity then. From building mess to mass, and shields are up in solid white. Thought black but who&amp;rsquo;s who and christ what colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RESET</title>
      <link>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/reset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 16:35:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/reset/</guid>
      <description>As we cross over the anniversary of COVID (for me born sometime during the Tết 2020 holidays, aka lunar new year), I want to start sharing my ideas for the new age. This blog will act as an inquiry into those ideas, and a space for them to grow.
If you thought you could skip the years between idealogical discovery and social implementation, you have already contributed to the downfall of humankind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Friend</title>
      <link>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 18:49:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.maxfettes.com/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>This is my first guest post on my brothers site!
 I know lots of quotes!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.maxfettes.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 18:48:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.maxfettes.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there after only two or three minutes, and as many years, mfbu navigates nvim in ranger; a wonder to the middling technician, set up by his technichian brother; and gets self access to the backend of his very own posting house. welcome seldom wanderer, this is a safe place. projects of the poetic include: dramatic samizdat sources into emergence and singularity, spontaneous economic theory of planet x, automatic film review (including speculation and gossip), anecdata, dotings, self quotes and a healthy dose of robot overlords.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>